decisiondesk.com 2014-11-23

# Privacy Policy | DecisionDesk

## Privacy Policy

**Last Revision -  April 29th, 2013**

It is the policy of DecisionDesk Inc. to respect the privacy of each person or entity using our products and/or services the Software Product (each, a “User”). We provide this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”) we receive when you visit and use our website, at [www.decisiondesk.com](http://decisiondesk.com/) (the “Website”). This Privacy Policy applies only to information that you provide to DecisionDesk through the Website or that is automatically collected when you access, download, purchase or use any information, services, products or content appearing on the Website.

## CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Website only collects, uses and/or discloses the personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify minors under the age of 13 after obtaining verifiable consent from a parent or guardian. If you are under age 13, or if you are the parent or guardian of person under age 13 whose personal information may be provided to DecisionDesk through the Website, please review the notices and disclosures located at <http://decisiondesk.com/privacy-policy-underage/>

We require those who are age 13 or over, but under the age of majority, obtain permission from a parent or guardian before utilizing the Website and we further recommend such minors obtain permission from a parent or guardian before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

## THE PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you register to become a User or otherwise utilize the Website, you may submit Personal Information. Personal Information may include, but is not limited to, your name, phone number and e-mail address. DecisionDesk may also collect Personal Information from you if you choose to opt-in to participate in applications, sweepstakes, surveys, contests or competitions. When you register with DecisionDesk, you create your own profile for the purpose of submitting audition recordings or applying to contests, awards, events, universities, etc. Your profile information, as well as your name, e-mail and photo, are displayed to those who or that you have specified in your audition or application. Profile information you submit to DecisionDesk, and make public via any public audition or application process, may also be available to other Users or those using the Website and may be available to third party search engines. We recommend that you guard your anonymity and sensitive information to the extent that you upload any public auditions or applications. We are not responsible for any Personal Information you chose to disclose publically on the Website.

## USE AND DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

The Personal Information we collect, including your profile information, name, email and photo, will be used to submit audition recordings or to apply to items such as, but not limited to, programs, contests, awards, events or university admission offered by other users of the Website specified in such User’s application (each, a “Reviewer”). Each Reviewer will be permitted to use the information in the same manner as if you applied for the program directly with such Reviewer. DecisionDesk makes no endorsement or representations and is not responsible regarding the information privacy practices of any Reviewer. You should review the terms and conditions, including the information, privacy and other policies and practices, of any Reviewer before any information is submitted using the Website.

Personal Information is also used (1) to provide and improve our services, features and content, (2) to administer your use of our services and your DecisionDesk account, (3) to enable you to enjoy and easily navigate the Website, (4) to better understand your needs and interests, (5) to fulfill requests you may make, (6) to personalize your experience, (7) to provide service announcements and (8) to provide you with further information and offers from us or third parties you may find useful or interesting, including newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information on our services. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive any such communications, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any such communication. Further, your privacy and email settings may be easily adjusted via your account settings at any time.

We may employ third party service providers to provide services on our behalf or to perform services related to administration of the Website (including, without limitation, maintenance, hosting and database management services, web analytics, payment processing and administration). These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to the extent necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use your Personal Information for any other purpose.

Except as otherwise provided elsewhere in this policy, DecisionDesk will not disclose your Personal Information obtained through the Website to third parties other than DecisionDesk’s service providers, affiliates, vendors and business partners unless DecisionDesk has the good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to:  
cooperate with law enforcement authorities or comply with legal process served on DecisionDesk or any such service provider, affiliate, vendor or business partner;

protect the property and rights of DecisionDesk and such service providers, affiliates, vendors and business partners;

protect the safety of the public or any person;

prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable;

complete, as permitted by law, a business sale, asset transfer, merger, acquisition or reorganization; or  
fix or debug problems with the Website or DecisionDesk’s servers, software or service.

## LOGGING AND COOKIES

As you use the Website, our servers automatically record information that the browser sends whenever it points to a Website or online service (“Log Data”). Log Data may include, but is not limited to, a computer’s Internet Protocol address, browser type, the web page visited before arriving at the Website and information searched for, or viewed, on the Website and information related to any music listening habits on the Website and the profile information viewed via the Website.

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to a computer for record-keeping purposes. We use “persistent cookies” to save usernames and passwords for future logins to the Website. We use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of our service, to better understand how the User interacts with the Website, to monitor web traffic routing on the Website and to monitor aggregate usage of the Website. Certain browsers can be instructed to stop accepting cookies and/or to issue a prompt before accepting a cookie. If a browser being used by a User does not accept cookies, that User may not be able to use all portions of the Website or all functionality of our services.

We may share aggregated information that includes non-identifying information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services, all for the sole benefit of DecisionDesk. Users and others using the Website will not be compensated such aggregated or non-identifying information.

## PUBLICLY AVAILABLE INFORMATION

In addition to your username, any comments or submissions that you post to the Website may be publicly available. You post and share your Personal Information and content on the Website at your own risk. While we go to great lengths to create a safe and enjoyable experience on the Website, we cannot control the actions of other users with whom you may choose to share your content and/or profile information or institutions to which you submit applications and auditions. In addition, we cannot anticipate other users’ ability to circumvent privacy settings. You acknowledge that, even after removal of your Personal Information and content from the Website, copies of your information may remain viewable in cached or archived Web pages or on the local computers of users who may have downloaded or stored your information. Even with all the appropriate precautions DecisionDesk takes to protect your information, we recommend you refrain from sending private information or Personal Information by e-mail, chat, or other messaging services.

## CHANGING OR DELETING YOUR INFORMATION

You may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in your registration profile by logging into your account and changing the “user preferences” associated with your account. If you completely delete all such information, your account may be deactivated. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes.

## SECURITY

DecisionDesk is concerned with safeguarding your information. We use a variety of industry-standard measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.

## INTERNATIONAL TRANSFER

Your information may be transferred to, and maintained on, computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. If you are located outside the United States and choose to provide information to DecisionDesk, please be advised that we transfer Personal Information to the United States and process it there. Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

## Third Party Sites and Sponsors

DecisionDesk does not engage third parties to solicit or advertise to any User via the Website. DecisionDesk makes no endorsement of or representations regarding, and may not be deemed responsible for, the information, privacy or other practices of any website that is linked to the Website. Any advertisers or others with websites linked to the Website may have their own terms and conditions. You should review any such terms and conditions, including the information, privacy and other policies and practices, prior to accessing or further using such advertisers’ or others’ websites.

## Consumer Education Related to Social Networking

Creating a safe social networking environment is important to DecisionDesk. For additional information interested persons may visit the following links created by the Federal Trade Commission to learn more about social networking safety tips:

<http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking.html>

<http://onguardonline.gov/socialnetworking_youth.html>

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

Except as otherwise provided below, we reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice and any such changes shall be effective upon our posting of any such change. Please (1) review this Privacy Policy from time to time to review the most up-to-date version and (2) that your continued use of the Website subsequent to any such changes constitutes your acceptance of such changes. We will provide notice to you of, or obtain your consent to, these changes where required by applicable law.

## Contacting DecisionDesk

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@decisiondesk.com](mailto:privacy@decisiondesk.com). You may also contact us by mail at 14805 Detroit Ave., Suite 320, Lakewood, OH 44107.

## Your California Privacy Rights

A business subject to California Civil Code section 1798.83 is required to disclose to its California customers, upon request, the identity of any third parties to whom the business has disclosed personal information within the previous calendar year, along with the type of personal information disclosed, for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes.

If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please send an email to [privacy@decisiondesk.com](mailto:privacy@decisiondesk.com).
